Finding aid for Bentley Historical Library records, 1919 - 2014
Bentley Historical Library
- Administrative Records, 1935-2013; 25 linear feet
  - Francis X. Blouin (1981-2013)
    - Director's Office/Central Files
      - Topical Files
        - Audio-visual conversion -- Scene Savers, 2008 (Box 56)
        - Bentley 75th Anniversary Celebration (Box 56)
          - General, 2008-2010 (Box 56)
          - Dinner, 2010 (Box 56)
          - Made in Michigan Concert, 2010 (Box 56)
          - Street banners, 2010 (Box 56)
          - Whiting Room Display, 2009-2010; 3 folders (Box 56)
        - Bentley Image Bank, 1998 (Box 56)
        - Bentley reorganization, 2011 (Box 56)
        - BHL Building Addition, 2001-2002 (Box 77)
        - Birkerts book, 2007 (Box 56)
        - Blouin, Francis (Box 56)
          - Curriculum Vitae, 2013 (Box 56)
          - Retirement, 2012 (Box 56)
          - Vita documentation, 1975-2013; 5 folders (Box 56)
        - Budget meeting, 2005 (Box 56)
        - Capital request -- IT Council, 2012 (Box 56)
        - China Index 2006 (Partnerships, Programs, Projects, People), 2006 (Box 56)
        - Collection development, 1992-1997 (Box 56)
        - Collection development, 2013 (Box 56)
        - Collections division, 1982-1986 (Box 56)
        - Committee on Institutional Conflict of Interest in Clinical Trials, 2011 (Box 56)
        - Conservation, 1974-1989
        - Controlling the Past, 2003 (Box 57)
        - Cost study of preservation options -- Ann Flowers, 1994 (Box 57)
        - Council on Library and Information Resources, 1999 (Box 77)
        - Cultural Collections Council, 2011-2012 (Box 57)
        - Deans and Executive Officers Letters, 2012 (Box 57)
        - Deans presentations, 2008-2012 (Box 57)
        - Deep Blue, 2004-2005 (Box 57)
        - Detroit Observatory, 2005-2006; 2 folders (Box 77)
        - Development, 1984-1991 (Box 57)
        - Development -- Campaign for Michigan Library Case Statement, 1993-1995 (Box 57)
        - Digital assets staff retreat, 2011 (Box 57)
        - Digital Curation, 2011-2012 (Box 57)
        - Digital Curation Manual, 2011 (Box 57)
        - Dillard, Angela: Black Churches, 2007 (Box 57)
        - Eisenberg Seminar, 2004-2009 (Box 57)
        - Fleming Basement, 1992-2001 (Box 77)
        - Ford Presidential Library, 1987-2006 (Box 57)
        - Ford Presidential Library Advisory Committee, 1998-2001 (Box 77)
        - Ford School, 2011 (Box 57)
        - General Motors Tech Center, 2012 (Box 57)
        - Google Project, 2006 (Box 57)
        - Governors' Papers, 1973-2005; 4 folders (Box 57)
        - Hedstrom, Margaret -- Consultation on Bentley and Digital Environment, 1995-1996 (Box 57)
        - Historic Preservation Guild of Bay View, 1989 (Box 57)
        - Historical Society of Michigan, 2002 (Box 77)
        - History Department Newsletter: News from the Bentley, 1982-1994 (Box 57)
        - History and Traditions Committee (Box 57)
          - General, 2002-2010; 3 folders (Box 57)
          - Michigan Union Project, undated (Box 57)
          - North Hall, 2005 (Box 57)
          - Peckham royalty question, 1992-2009 (Box 57)
          - Simpson Institute, 1998-2007 (Box 57)
        - IT Rationalization: Paul Courant, 2010 (Box 58)
        - Job Description, Assistant Director, 1986 (Box 58)
        - Joint archival facility, 2010 (Box 58)
        - Kellogg Digitization Project, 2011 (Box 58)
        - Kellogg Foundation, 1997 (Box 58)
        - Kemmerer, Aleandra: Eric Stein Papers, 2011 (Box 58)
        - M-Pathways Project, 1998-1999 (Box 58)
        - M-Quality and the Bentley, 1993 (Box 58)
        - Making of America Project, 1993-1994 (Box 58)
        - Making of America Project, 2003 (Box 58)
        - Making of American Project, 2006 (Box 58)
        - Medical Center Documentation Initiative, 1992 (Box 58)
        - Mellon Foundation: Automated Processing Proposal, 2012 (Box 58)
        - Mellon Foundation: Case Studies and the Effective Management of University Digital Records, 2006-2007 (Box 58)
        - MeMail, 2010-2011 (Box 58)
        - MeMail -- Early meeting with John King and Laura Patterson, 2003-2009 (Box 58)
        - Michigan Detroit Observatory, 2000 (Box 58)
        - Michigan Modern Exhibition -- Cranbrook Art Museum, 2013 (Box 58)
        - Millennium Project Faculty History Website, 2006-2009 (Box 58)
        - Mold, 1992-2000 (Box 78)
        - National Historical Publications and Records Commission (NHPRC) State Historic Records Board (SHRB), 1986-2010; 5 folders (Box 58)
        - New directorship, 1980 (Box 58)
        - Observatory clock, 1980 (Box 58)
        - Office of General Council Task Force, 2011 (Box 58)
        - Organization of American Historians, 1974-1985 (Box 58)
        - Patient Records, 2006 (Box 58)
        - Patterson, Laura, 2011 (Box 58)
        - Port Huron Statement 50-Year Commemoration, 2012 (Box 58)
        - Printed works, 1976-1987 (Box 58)
        - Public Goods Council, 1999-2011; 3 folders
        - Public Goods Council -- Deaccessioning, 2003-2004 (Box 59)
        - Public Goods Council -- Postdoctoral Fellowship Mellon Grant, 2001 (Box 59)
        - Rackham 100th Anniversary Celebration Planning, 2008-2009 (Box 59)
        - Records Management, 1981-1986 (Box 59)
        - Records Management Task Force, 2012 (Box 59)
        - Reference, 1979-1998 (Box 59)
        - Regents correspondence, 1993-1996 (Box 59)
        - Regents, history of, 1986 (Box 59)
        - Salary Equity Study, 2010 (Box 59)
        - Sawyer Seminar bibliography, 2000 (Box 59)
        - Sawyer Seminar proposals and planning, 1997-2002 (Box 59)
        - SharePoint, 2008 (Box 59)
        - Sligh Furniture Co. Project, 1979 (Box 59)
        - Snyder, Rick (Gov.), 2012 (Box 59)
        - Space
          - BHL Addition, 2001 (Box 78)
          - Buildings, 1990-2000 (Box 78)
          - Security, 1992-1998 (Box 78)
          - Statistics, 1999 (Box 59)
        - Staff computer upgrades, 2010 (Box 59)
        - Staff Meeting Minutes, 2000-2001 (Box 79)
        - Statistics for acquisitions, processing, reference and professional staff activities, 1995 (Box 59)
        - Talks, 2000-2010 (Box 59)
          - "Email as Archives" Kernochan Center for Law, Media and the Arts at Columbia Law School, 2010 (Box 59)
          - "Definition of the Historical Record in a Time of Rapid Technological Advancement" Midwest Archives Conference Plenary, 2000 (Box 59)
          - "Evolving Relationship between Archives and Academic History" American Historical Association, 2005 (Box 59)
          - "Hidden Collections Keynote" Council for Library and Information Resources (CLIR), 2010 (Box 59)
          - "Thoughts on Special Collections" 50th Anniversary Rare Book and Manuscript Section (RBMS) of the American Library Association (ALA), 2009 (Box 59)
          - "Vatican Archives and Constructs of the Past" Canfield Lecture, Sacred Heart Seminary, Detroit, 2001 (Box 59)
        - Tappan's glass, 2001 (Box 59)
        - Transition planning, 2012 (Box 59)
        - UARP and Margie Barritt transition, 1998 (Box 59)
        - University of Michigan Bicentennial Heritage Project, 2009 (Box 59)
        - University of Michigan Bicentennial Planning Committee, 2011-2012; 2 folders (Box 59)
        - University of Michigan Dearborn Archives, 2012 (Box 59)
        - University of Michigan Museum of Art (UMMA) Agreement, 2012 (Box 59)
        - Virakhovskaya, Olga -- Position reclassification, 2010 (Box 59)
        - Wallach/Craven/Powers Retirement Event, 2012 (Box 59)
        - Ward, Willis -- Commemoration, 2012 (Box 59)
        - Warner, Robert -- Paperless Office, 1982 (Box 59)
        - Wayne State: Great Lakes Books, 1986-1996 (Box 59)
        - Weiss, Janet, 2010-2012 (Box 59)
        - Whitesell Lectures, 2006-2012 (Box 59)
      - International
        - Bosnia, 1999 (Box 59)
        - China [See also, box 21 for 1998-1999], 1995-1997 (Box 59)
        - China, 2000-2001 (Box 59)
        - China, 2006-2013; 7 folders (Box 60)
        - China: State Archives Administration of China Exchange Agreements, 1999-2009 (Box 60)
        - Cuba, 1997-2000 (Box 60)
        - Denmark, 2009-2010; 2 folders (Box 60)
        - European correspondence, 1984-1998 (Box 60)
        - France -- Institut national du patrimoine, 1991-2012 (Box 60)
          - General correspondence, 1992-2004 (Box 60)
          - INP, 2005 (Box 60)
          - Internships, 1991-1996 (Box 60)
          - Barbance, Celine, 1994 (Box 60)
          - Barbat, Philippe, 1997 (Box 60)
          - Basques, Valerie, 1992 (Box 60)
          - DuMalle, Bergangere, 2006-2007 (Box 60)
          - Duvigneu, Marion, 1993 (Box 60)
          - Foucher, Jean Pascal, 1995-1996 (Box 60)
          - Kinossian, Yves, 1995 (Box 60)
          - Leroy, Aubin, 2005-2006 (Box 60)
          - Martin, Claire, 2004 (Box 60)
          - Olive, Beatrice, 1999 (Box 60)
          - Sablon du Corail, Amable, 2002 (Box 60)
          - Verdo, Remy, 2011-2012 (Box 60)
        - International Seminar Ann Arbor, 1997 (Box 60)
        - Italy -- American Academy in Rome, 1991-1993 (Box 60)
        - Italy -- Consultancy for Medici Archive Project, 2009 (Box 60)
        - Russia, 1993-2006; 5 folders (Box 60)
        - South Africa, 1998; 2003; 2 folders
        - Vatican, 1997-2001 (Box 60)
        - Vatican Archives book: Contracts and Releases, 1994-2001 (Box 60)
        - Vatican Archives book: Correspondence, 1992-1998 (Box 60)
      - Staff
        - Staff recommendation files, alphabetical [, 1980-2008 (Box 15)
          [Restricted until July 01, 2043 ]
    - Staff
      - Boles, Frank Departure, 1991 (Box 8)
        (includes snapshot photographs)
      - Bordin Gillette Researcher Travel Fellowship, 1990-1996 (Box 8)
      - Fine, Sidney Retirement (Box 8)
      - Pugh, Mary Jo Interview with Marjorie Barritt (transcript), 1984 (Box 8)
      - Pugh, Mary Jo Farewell Party, 2 folders (Box 8)
      - General (Box 8)
      - Job Descriptions (Box 8)
      - Church History Conference, 1983 (Box 8)
      - Conservation, 1980 (Box 8)
      - Diplomatics Conference, 1992 (Box 8)
    - Conferences and Events
      - Electronic Records Conference, 1996 (Box 8)
      - Fiftieth Anniversary Celebration of the MHC
        - 50th Anniversary Committee, Diane Hatfield, 1985 (Box 8)
        - Banquet, September 20, 1985 (Box 8)
        - "Michigan Promise and Performance Exhibit,", 1984-1985 (Box 8)
        - International Seminar, 1997 (Box 8)
      - Lunch Series, circa 1986 (Box 8)
      - Second European Conference
        - General, 1989 (Box 8)
        - Speeches, 1989 (Box 8)
      - Visual Culture and Archives Symposium
        - April 4, 2013
          - Welcome and Introductory Remarks (Nancy Bartlett), .MP4 video
          - "Images and Archives: Visual, Visceral, Virtual"
            - Chair, Teresa Brinati, .MP4 video
            - Speaker, Joan Schwartz, .MP4 video
            - Commentary, Terry Cook, .MP4 video
          - "All the Art of the Earth": Albert Renger-Patzsch and the Folkwang Verlag
            - Chair, Nancy Deromedi, .MP4 video
            - Speaker, Pepper Stetler, .MP4 video
          - "Archives of Architecture: Images and Imaginations"
            - Chair, Joe Rosa, .MP4 video
            - Speaker, Kent Kleinman: "Touching Architecture", .MP4 video
            - Speaker, Claire Zimmerman: "Albert Kahn Project", .MP4 video
            - Speaker, John Comazzi: "Anticipating the Archive"
            - Panel Discussion, .MP4 video
          - "Archives, Information Design, and Visualization
            - Chair, Laura Patterson, .MP4 video
            - Speaker, Kilian Krug: "Visual Access to Archives", .MP4 video
            - Speaker, Jonathan Massey: "Seeing Time and Space", .MP4 video
          - "Body Poetics in the Time of Digital Babel: The Screendancer as Poet/Archivist"
            - Chair, Angela Kane, .MP4 video
            - Speaker, Peter Sparling, .MP4 video
          - "Photographer Jerzy Lewczynski: Performing the Archives"
            - Chair, Olga Virakhovskaya, .MP4 video
            - Speaker, Krzysztof Pijarski, .MP4 video
          - "From Film to Screen: Images, Editing, and Archives"
            - Chair, Jim Tobin, .MP4 video
            - Speaker, Jay Cassidy, .MP4 video
        - April 5, 2013
          - "Archives, Evidence, and Visualization
            - Chair, Michael Shallcross, .MP4 video
            - Speaker, Vicki Lemieux: "Visualizing Archives: Cognitive and Perceptual Dimensions", .MP4 video
            - Speaker, Maria Esteva: "Anatomy of Big Archives Visualization", .MP4 video
            - Speaker, Brien Brothman: "Reading Pictures, Picturing Texts: Random Observations", .MP4 video
          - "Identifying Images, Negotiating Archives"
            - Chair, Joseph Ho, .MP4 video
            - Speaker, Carla Sinopoli: "Texts, Images and Objects: Tracing the Himalayan Journey of Walter Norman Koelz", .MP4 video
            - Speaker, Karolina Ziebinska-Lewandowska: "The Archives as Object and Place of Mourning", .MP4 video
            - Speaker, Ricardo Laquilac Punzalan: "Return by Surrogacy: Digital Representation, Virtual Reunification, and Ethnographic Archival Images", .MP4 video
          - "Using Digitized Photographs: Two Models
            - Chair, Jarrett M. Drake, .MP4 video
            - Speaker, Paul Conway, .MP4 video
          - "Rauschenberg's Archives"
            - Chair, Nancy Bartlett, .MP4 video
            - Speaker, Graham Smith, .MP4 video
          - "Forward Perspectives", .MP4 video
            - Chair, Nancy Bartlett
            - Commentary, Mary
            - Panelist, Terry Cook
            - Panelist, Joan Schwartz
          - Final Remarks (Francis Blouin), .MP4 video
          - Tribute to Francis X. Blouin
            - Moderator, Paul Courant, .MP4 video
            - Speaker, William G. Rosenberg, .MP4 video
            - Speaker, Angela Dillard, .MP4 video
            - Speaker, Hank Meijer, .MP4 video
            - Speaker, Terry Cook, .MP4 video
            - Presentation of Gifts (Leonard Coombs, Diane Hatfield, Greg Kinney, Bruce Madej, and Francis Blouin), .MP4 video
        - Photographs, 2013
          - Selected Panelists, April 4, 2013; .ZIP file
          - Tribute and Reception, April 5, 2013; .ZIP file
        - Poster, 2013; .PDF file
        - Program, 2013; .PDF file
    - Special Projects
      - Activities & Initiatives: A Report of a Public Good, 1998-1999 (Box 9)
      - Alumnae Surveys (Box 9)
      - American Archivist Issue on Diplomatics, 1993 (Box 9)
      - American Institutions Program, 1983-1984 (Box 9)
      - Bentley Library Building Addition Dedication, 2004 (Box 9)
      - Black Women in the Midwest, 1983 (Box 9)
      - Burk, Marty Project (Box 9)
      - Chelsea NHPRC Grant Program, 1995-1996 (Box 9)
      - Davenport, Horace (History of UM Medical School), 1984-1985 (Box 9)
      - Detroit and the Great Migration, 1990-1991 (Box 9)
      - Detroiter Abend-Post Newspaper Microfilming, 1981-1982 (Box 9)
      - Detroit Race Riot (1967) Oral History Project, 1984 (Box 9)
      - Governor's Papers, 1986 (Box 9)
      - Hagley Museum Project (Box 9)
      - Jessye, Eva Collection (Review) Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 9)
      - Labadie Collection Processing Grant (NEH), 1982-1984 (Box 9)
      - Michigan Historical Collection: Collection Review, 2005 (Box 9)
      - Michigan State University, Micro-Marc Computer Software Grant, 1984-1987 (Box 9)
      - NARA Appraisal Project, 1989 (Box 9)
      - Penn-Central Railroad Project, 1984-1985 (Box 9)
      - Preservation Microfilming Proposal (NEH), 1985 (Box 9)
      - Rackham 50th Anniversary, 1986-1988 (Box 9)
      - Records Management Policy Development, 1988 (Box 9)
      - Richard, Gabriel Commemorative Volume, 1984-85 (Box 9)
      - SI Electronic Records, 1997 (Box 9)
      - Richard, Gabriel: Intellectual Life on the Michigan Frontier: The Libraries of Gabriel Richard & John Monteith
        - Index cards, 2 boxes (Box 10)
        - Galley proofs, 5 folders (Box 10)
      - Vatican Archives Project
        - Correspondence Files, 1984-2005; 21 folders (Box 11)
        - Proposal, Grants, accounts, etc., 1978-1986 (Box 11)
        - Grant Files
          - American Friends of the Vatican Library, 1988-1989 (Box 11)
          - Delmas Foundation, 2002-2004 (Box 11)
          - Getty Grant Project, 1988-1995 (Box 11)
          - Guggenheim Foundation Initiative, 1994-1996 (Box 11)
          - Lilly Endowment, Inc., 1992-1995 (Box 11)
          - Mellon Foundation, 1992-1996 (Box 11)
          - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1990-1994 (Box 12)
          - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1988-1991; 2 folders (Box 12)
          - Office for the Vice President of Research (University of Michigan), 1986 (Box 12)
          - Samuel Kress Foundation, 1991 (Box 12)
        - Topical Files
          - Ademecum Procedures Library and Archive, circa 1986-1996 (Box 12)
          - Agreements, 1988-1992 (Box 12)
          - American Academy in Rome, 1988-1989; 2002 (Box 12)
          - Archivi and Computers Article, 1993 (Box 12)
          - Archives Nationales, Paris Archives Nationales, 1978; undated (Box 12)
          - Archivio Segreto Vaticano (ASV) Inventory, 2004 (Box 12)
          - Beth's Early Work, 1991; 1994; undated (Box 12)
          - Canfield Lecture, 2001 (Box 12)
          - Cataloging Records GEAC Library System, 1987 (Box 12)
          - Cataloging Manual and Authorities, 1987 (Box 12)
          - Comitato Scientifico CDF, 1996-2003 (Box 12)
          - Dinner for Leonard Boyle, 1998 (Box 12)
          - Fabbrica di San Petro, 1994-1995; undated (Box 12)
          - First Worksheet, 1987 (Box 12)
          - History of Art Section, 1987-1988 (Box 12)
          - Homeland Foundation Conference, 1992 (Box 12)
          - International Business Machine (IBM) Project, 1992-1994 (Box 12)
          - Italian Academy for Advanced Studies in America, 1992-1996 (Box 12)
          - Kristeller, Paul Oskar, circa 1993; undated (Box 12)
          - Location Maps, undated (Box 12)
          - Notes on Bulk, undated (Box 12)
          - Oxford University Press, 1995-1998 (Box 12)
          - Publication, An Inventory and Guide to Historical Documents of the Holy See (Supplement 1), 2003 (Box 12)
          - Publications (Box 13)
            - Vatican Archives: An Inventory and Guide to Historical Documents of the Holy See, 1998 (Box 13)
          - Propaganda Fide, undated (Box 13)
          - Photographs (black and white), undated (Box 13)
          - Photographs (negatives), undated (Box 13)
          - Photographic Slides, circa 1990-1991 (Box 13)
          - Post info, 1922; undated (Box 13)
          - Project Books Purchased, undated (Box 13)
          - Project for Congregation for the Doctrine of the Faith, 1998-2004 (Box 13)
          - Project Description (English and Italian), 1989 (Box 13)
          - Project Publicity, 1989-1991 (Box 13)
          - Reference File, 1986-1991 (Box 13)
          - Report, 1990 (Box 13)
          - Reverend Leonard Boyle Obituary, circa 1999 (Box 13)
          - RLIN Catalog Records/RLIN System, 1991-1996 (Box 13)
          - Rockefeller Archive Center materials on Vatican Library Project (W. Bishop), 1998 (Box 13)
          - Rome Trip, 1987 (Box 13)
          - Scope and Content, undated (Box 13)
          - Source Notes, 1992; undated (Box 13)
          - Sister Claudia Carlen, 2004 (Box 13)
          - Staff Matters, 1989-1997 (Box 13)
          - Trinity College Dublin, 1996; undated (Box 13)
          - Vatican Library, undated (Box 13)
          - Web page text, undated (Box 13)
        - Examples from Project (photocopy material)
          - ASU Agostiniani II (Box 14)
          - Bandi Sciolti Notations, 1425-1571; 2 folders (Box 14)
          - Bandi Sciolti Notations, 1561-1846 (Box 14)
          - Collectoria 85 inventories (Box 14)
          - Collectoria 477 Spole to Monastery, 1367 (Box 14)
          - Index of Indexes, 1901 (Box 14)
          - Index Fondo Albani 267 Clement IX (Box 14)
          - Index Servita Minyta v. 1 (Box 14)
          - Institutional Miscellaneous (Box 14)
          - Inventory Eccelesstical Yearbooks 14 c (Juste Miscellaneous N. 5342 II) (Box 14)
          - Inventory and Part Fondo Albani (Box 14)
          - Inventory Fondo Basiliani (Box 14)
          - Inventory and Documents Miscellaneous Arm II (Box 14)
          - Rubricellae Camera Apostolica (Box 14)
          - Rota Decisiones, 1600-1608 (Box 14)
          - Supplications, Reg 267 (Box 14)
        - Reference Files (photocopy material
          - ASU and Research (Box 14)
          - Avignon (Box 14)
          - Barbiche "Apostolic Chancery" (Box 14)
          - Barberini Mss (Box 14)
          - Calendar of State Papers UK (Box 14)
          - Chancery Henry III (Box 14)
          - Congregation of the Council (Box 14)
          - Curial Pronouncements (Box 14)
          - Guide du Vatican (Box 14)
          - Inventaires du Vatican (Box 14)
          - Kristeller IterItalieum (Box 14)
          - Maria Grazia Pastura Ruggiero, "La Computisteria generle organizza la consultabilitia del proprio archivio alla fine del secolo XVIII" (Box 14)
          - Oliver Poneet, "Segereteria dei brevi" (Box 14)
          - Peter Partner, Papal Financial Policy (Box 14)
          - Papal Registries UK (Box 14)
          - Roman Families (Box 14)
          - Ruspoli Docs on Handel (Box 14)
  - Terrence J. McDonald (2013-)
    - Conferences and Events
      - Aeon Symposium, 2016
        (The University of Michigan Bentley Historical Library, Special Collections Library, and William L. Clements Library are pleased to announce an Aeon Symposium dedicated to Connecting Uses, Pushing Limits among current and prospective institutional users of Aeon. From early adapters to newest users, participants will have the opportunity to affirm what's best and challenge the rest.)
        - Aeon Reports Workshop
          This interactive workshop will allow participants to gain experience in creating reports from Aeon data. Presentations will include basic report creation, to more advanced topics, such as translating management's questions into queries that Aeon can answer and overcoming obstacles. The format of the workshop will be a combination of short presentations and collaborative time for participants to ask questions and work on their own reporting challenges.
          Speakers: Matthew Adair, Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan; Kate Hutchens, Special Collections Library, University of Michigan; and Katie Gillespie, Atlas Systems
        - Aeon Roundtable
          (Aeon update and audience Q&A with Atlas Systems facilitated by Genie Powell.)
        - Atlas-ArchivesSpace Update
          (Aeon and ArchivesSpace discussion with Genie Powell of Atlas Systems and Christine Di Bella of ArchivesSpace.)
        - Friday Keynote--Kate Hutchens and Moira Fitzgerald
          The recent proliferation of Aeon implementations has taken place during a time when many libraries and archives have experienced a decrease in resources even as we strive to increase efforts towards outreach, discovery, digitization, and instruction. Aeon's tailored functionality has given us a specialized tool to manage these activities and many more. Equally important, this software enabled many of us to more efficiently collect data about this work, which has become increasingly important in the prevailing culture of assessment at many of our institutions.